{
    "subject": "resource/James_Kay_(Kentucky_politician)",
    "predicate": "property/almaMater",
    "object": "resource/University_of_Kentucky_College_of_Law",
    "human_readable": "James Kay (Kentucky politician) attended University of Kentucky College of Law.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9644418358802795,
            "question": "What field of study did James Kay pursue at the University of Kentucky College of Law?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8943732976913452,
            "question": "Did James Kay graduate from a university in Kentucky?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8870645761489868,
            "question": "What degree did James Kay likely earn from the University of Kentucky College of Law?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8550575375556946,
            "question": "Where did James Kay attend law school?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8001556992530823,
            "question": "What type of institution is the University of Kentucky College of Law?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7477601170539856,
            "question": "What is the full name of the university where James Kay studied law?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6094032526016235,
            "question": "Is James Kay involved in politics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5724400877952576,
            "question": "What state is James Kay associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5412676334381104,
            "question": "What is James Kay's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5351439118385315,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about James Kay's political career?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=James Kay (Kentucky politician) attended University of Kentucky College of Law.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3560_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is James Kay's profession?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3560_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What state is James Kay associated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3560_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is James Kay involved in politics?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3560_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3560_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3560_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3560_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3560_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3560_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3560_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3560_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3560_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3560_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3560_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that James L. Kay II earned his JD from the University of Kentucky College of Law, which supports the statement that he attended the University of Kentucky College of Law."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"James Kay (Kentucky politician) attended University of Kentucky College of Law.\" Specifically, the document states: \"Kay earned his BA in history and political science from the University of Kentucky and his JD from University of Kentucky College of Law.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}